hey guys this is Metro and today we're
going to be doing a review of my
Hyperlite Mountain gear Unbound twers
tent so let's keep moving okay so in
this video I'm going to give you a
highle overview of some of the features
that I like in this tent versus other
tents that I've had in the past so if
you're into that stuff make sure you
stick around to the very end what I
really like about this tent versus my
prior tent which was the zpack duplex l
is a couple of things one being this
waterproof zipper I'll go ahead and show
you a vestibule on the other side with
it fully extended and I'll start to make
my way on the inside but as you can see
there's a waterproof zipper here that's
nice because my previous uh tent had a
toggle here waterproof zipper going down
has these vents here if you've had a
dyema tent you probably know that these
tents tend to get a lot of condensation
so having this vent here is awesome
because it allows a little bit more
breathing to happen so you don't get so
much condensation on the inside of the
tent but as we continue on you'll also
see at the top here it's got these
reinforced tops um as you start to use
dyema uh over and over and over again
this fabric will eventually start to uh
stretch a little bit so this helps
reinforce those areas where the tension
is going to be I've rolled up the
vestibule here and as you can see it has
these magnetic toggles very easy to
latch those on love that because when
you're trying to get these things up and
down during a rainstorm that makes it
really easy another thing that I like is
going to be the zipper as you can see
I'm doing this with one hand with the
zpx duplex L I would have to use two
hands uh to use the rainbow door to get
in this is really easy to get into but
there's also a toggle as I continue down
up here if I wanted to take the mesh up
so this is composed of dcf1 and DCF 5 I
believe the thicker material is going to
be down here at the bottom with the
dyema bathtub floor but what I'll do is
I'll go ahead and put the rest of my
items inside of this t so you can see it
but again in a beautiful view beautiful
place this tent's going to be out
tonight in some awesome elements we were
blessed with some great weather not like
Trail Days where it was just non-stop
rain for 3 Days okay so this tent comes
in at 22.5 o this is a twers tent which
provides plenty of room if you're using
this for one person roughly about 28
square ft so if you are looking for a
little bit of luxury say on trail this
tent is definitely your best bet so the
inside you got these little toggles here
or the little points where you can
attach
items run a rge line if you'd like you
got some organization pouches on the
inside so charger your
headlamp oh that nature it's really cool
is
having the M doors like
this single hand easy to get in and out
of
really enjoying this tent so far but
lots of room on the inside get up
61 got all my stuff organized on the
right side or left side here bring my
pack inside and the VES is big enough to
bring your chair on the inside I'll
just put up
61 and to give you the idea you
obviously sake this out a little bit
further if you need to but plenty of
headro so I pulled the mesh the door's
back back on both sides you can see it's
a nice view so if you just want to chill
in your tent fish the sunrise this is a
perfect tent for it obviously I have the
location to but and I really like how
this tent is set up it has been
incredible using it over the past 6
months and you know I have a number of
tents that I use at home for a number of
different reasons but this my friends is
one of my favorite tents I've ever owned
and I'm so glad that I upgraded from the
zpa duplex fell to this tent cannot
complain 100% hands down the best tent
I've ever owned so if you found any
value in this video please hit the like
button subscribe to my channel and send
me your comments as I do respond as
always thanks for watching but until
next time let's keep moving